Thank you Mr. President, and Mr. Public.
The first question is, what is more being for everybody?
Today, January 18, 2021.
But the invitation to the honor of my barbecue and the crowd, right here.
Mr. President, please, Scott, I'd like to thank you for the say
if you'd like to hear your first hearing.
I'd like to just counsel with my place again,
Direct with City.
I ask God that she walks over.
We have to listen to what's her family.
I ask God that you take the employees of the city and this great community.
the great community. I thank you for sending me your sentit to describe so we might
be safe. We love you and we appreciate you and I thank you for sending me your sentit
to describe the United States of America. And we do remember that for which it's saying
Our nation and our nation and in this will we believe our team is strong.
For a few of us thank the First Referring.
six, seven, six, seven, seven, seven, seven.
Are you satisfied with the status?
So the number, number, number, number, number, number, number, number.
I think there's a question on truck route, geodec,
or five odd months ago, at the start of the visit.
So this is John.
He's an Anderson Shining, if you remember, he did the geodec record
and there's an enzyme on the truck route,
and so those are the last things.
Whenever you think that record that make a person
after finding this, and kind of talk about the thickness of the
Haven't been sawing anything like that.
So this is John Potter for Anderson.
I guess I have Jason Eckhart here too.
So we went basically finished the chart graph.
We've been starting since I was in 2000.
We started and did parts of it.
And then we finally had to do the soil.
But since you were going to get a job as in the chart graph,
it's kind of been completed.
We did it.
We had a lot of traction.
Everything.
And what we did was we found that with a visual
of course, this was the one that I next to
a few on the state of the town.
It was pretty good in the fact.
But then other course of the town,
people went that, especially when we got down to the middle
to go to the next slide.
These are courses we took about eight years ago.
Basically, we went to become those four layers in the chart graph.
And obviously, the surface layer was just placed.
It didn't already start to be cracked.
And then we found three other layers on the...
Sometimes they were attacked like a deer.
But you can see the last layer, that was the oldest one,
and then if you go to the next slide, you'll see some of it.
We couldn't even keep it in it.
It didn't survive the core and process itself,
which would turn up through the back of the box.
And then if you go to the next slide.
So some of them went here.
This was, you know, eight now inches when it was core,
but when it came out of it, you know, it was wrong.
And normally we ask, well, you know,
and then a while we'll come out, you know,
pulling that because it's pretty, pretty strong.
And it just shows, in one sense, it shows Mark's,
it's like about the last and that role.
But it's primarily because it has a fairly thick,
we call it asphalt layer, but it's asphalt,
grassland has been cracked.
If you go to the next slide, so that one,
this happened to be the one we had here, we had gotten it full,
and you can see it goes good for layers.
So that's sense.
So consistency, pretty much across the truck out of the next slide.
And then even a job on that previous slide, I mean,
that show that it's been over a day before time.
Right?
So it kind of gave you an idea of how to come in the next slide.
And then some of them on here,
this is actually a concrete repair.
So I would say, every further, every other repair,
very, the core, we found a concrete repair,
someone had done it in the past.
And just to get over, so the truck out of the new
of the greatest in there for a long time.
But at this point, probably it's been years
that in the last one, the number, because it's just cracked,
so let's do it.
Now, I'm going to go to the next slide.
Again, this is one of the show that you essentially,
that was upon.
So, there was one time where we were looking at maybe the
acrylic and the whole layer of concrete, the whole building of asphalt.
But because of the fact that it's more gravel than essentially asphalt,
if we would want an advantage to buy a construction,
just like we had on the Main Street,
they were actually at the same issue as you.
So, we were looking at a concrete option on the way,
but now definitely, I think concrete,
and this is an interesting concrete with a fake subway
and some of them is the way to go.
Next slide.
Again, this is another floor.
Again, I would, of course, ask me, who went back
and we had, in the five or six different thoughts,
I think we had four here, test it here.
So, this was something I had done actually back in 2012
before we had the original thicknesses.
But what we did here was to fill in the blanks.
So, we did everything we had to pass,
and they showed me just adding to it,
to help save cost, and then make sure we do it something.
Essentially, we had the same three layers,
some of these nice four layers,
at least three layers, and they all have a time that's all which is.
So, there's going to be a pretty large asphalt section
to take out.
Next slide.
This was just showing, we did it pouring,
and I brought some of the sample,
but you were just, just touched the samples,
you would know that this is not an organ.
It's still very soft in the problem of the squeeze,
and it's very dangerous as you can see.
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze.
Because you're going to talk about that,
not because everybody comes in to see it.
It's always like, well, why do you think you're going to do this?
You know, we're going to drop them out and see it.
So one thing when you can see,
if you just look at this number here, we have a little test
that we run.
And normally, like, for example, in chocolate,
we might see numbers that are like two, three,
maybe sometimes four, or what we're doing
or two on an example.
We did that.
On the other hand, you're raised by a little near the road
to turn the after the parade.
Or we did those.
And those streets are fairly strong,
and you have fairly good and high, a lot content.
That was kind of gave my eye on the slow they had.
And the numbers that were getting, typically, you know,
0.5, 1.7 by just, it's just a kind of a mediocre strength.
It's what we have.
And that's why when you look at some of these old streets,
especially in the older parts city,
we'll see that those were made of concrete.
And I think they realized that was pretty much the only way
to make the streets last in the last, you know, long.
But that's why these numbers are lower.
These workers are lower.
And it just makes the, it just happens to be,
for the first three or four people.
Once you get to these four five, two people,
we have a higher strength soils.
But, you know, we'll remember the road that's, you know,
we'll remember two people.
And then often times, especially on the truck route,
the truck route, you know, we look the way back.
Sometimes the truck route, these, in these streets,
it was a residential street.
We went through one of them.
And now we've had to convert it to a truck route.
So some of the stormwater, things like that,
only we're never meant to be, you know,
having all these trucks to the river.
So with so much stormwater, you know,
it's also making the soil just stay saturated
with a little bit weaker.
These soil samples here that I had here.
They've been probably sitting in the lab for,
of course, about a month or two.
I think we came out here, you know,
November 18th, about two months.
They thought, I don't know.
I pulled them out for this, and all these ones were bad.
And then I said, oh, yeah, I need to have a little water
to get it back to where they were.
But just a little bit of water,
and I was six hours later, you know,
there aren't much water.
And that's the way these soils will be,
because they're always saturated.
So that was one of the reasons why we had,
you know, we needed to get this concrete just because
so many trucks on the other concrete provide this.
Of course, maybe in the city of Japan,
we might get away with six or ten inches of rock
to provide a good stable support here,
but the city is about 1816.
And they use that several times successfully.
And then part of that is it just needs
that distance to get from that salt or soil.
I've seen it many times when we were doing states
about the 2014, we put down the first eight inches of rock.
And sometimes that eight inches of rock
which is an island that's going to make it just the real too much.
But then it's put the eight.
and then it's stable, and get on there with the pain,
and put the tension, and trust the world over.
So that is the medicine, but the recognition
we're going to do with the truck around.
And then the other secondary, that have
that 16 inches of rock, we're going to recommend a rock
that is a little bit cleaner than that as much minuses of.
So when the water does get there, it'll be open.
We'll be locked.
We can't fix the slow water away, but we like to,
just because it's really cost-prepared.
So that clean rock can now be still watered by the trample rock.
So one of the things we've recommended is that we're already
able to spawn rocks, or we're going to put a pipe in just
like we did on Main Street, because of the water
that we're going to get into the rocks.
And I don't know if the streets last that much longer.
So if the very low cost option, they can throw out a wild rock.
But that in that show, we've got to be your source,
and that's the best way to do it.
I think it was going to be the water state with the concrete out.
We've gone through it with a lot of the water concrete streets.
We did just 10 years ago.
We were still holding up, really, this was the next one.
And this was just the show.
We had some of this, and this is one of the things we had done back in 2012.
And we did, and it's the mortgage, too, in between.
But normally, a job, we would have a CPR of anyone
from three to five to ten.
And the same, the CPR of three, it's a barrier, so it's a number of three.
It's not just too great if we want it.
It's three times a period of six months.
If you have a CPR of one, you can see that three, you take three to five to one.
That's three of a percentage of a month.
And that's one of the reasons why we did that.
We had to just have a little bit more concrete, a little bit more asphalt,
quite a bit more stability.
And then we had pretty much, okay, the middle, two thirds of land on it.
There's water, we have water problems, it just doesn't drain right to that.
That's partly what makes the CPR of this whole California barrier and nation.
It's a number of the tests you've put the strength in the stomach.
So it's just a little bit lower than here.
We didn't get started for about 22, 24 inches, and we've been okay.
We needed to be concrete, 16 inches of stone, that gets us in the 24, and that's kind of what we're
to see if I'm already, that's where this magic number is, and they've been doing all the repairs,
and they do the streets of cells, they do the typically the 20th branches, somewhere around that
range, because I think I'll let that go.
Next slide.
I don't know what happened here.
I think it was the trucks here, but basically, if you look at all the trucks, we've done a
drive the town, I think it's 2014, we worked with the public work, so I think we had
to train your guys, and they helped us count trucks, they kind of helped save costs, but essentially
we'll get done up with, they call it youths.
of global access when you see a truck running down the road, you have two access to the
back, two driving access, so those are four access.
And so, we need about five million access to those trucks to travel.
That's how we use the payment design.
And then go to the next slide.
And then when the math, the truck goes from the Senate and the students and things of the
package, that's what we came up with, the EHGs.
So this part of the design is really,
and then the survey is that the donations, now one,
you can find the geotec, the soil, the federal, and the capital,
and we need to pay them.
And then the next step to be started with the geotec,
the geometry of the payment design for the truck out,
is there a reason to improve the drainage, and then we'll go from,
in case the south side goes to the EHG tunnel.
And this was just the area across the chest, and the heads up, and we'll wrap it.
And then once we get out of the truck out there,
everything went to work, there's a series of streets that I think we call them,
the parking streets.
So 13 other streets are a potential, you know,
to go to the next slide.
Or they can slide through, you know, kind of trying to find some,
and you can use ways to make it all up a wall.
Each street has a slightly different approach that they're trying to use.
But the CDF, they're through, and you're there.
And then where we have to, we're going to find some,
you can use that for subcontract, okay.
So they may have any questions, but I'm sure we can do it,
and I'm not going to be just the next agenda.
I'll talk about it.
And what I'm going to do, did ask us, they have a schedule to do it,
but if we ever fix the truck out, they will not have a test
of tractor on their nose down through.
So I have a quick question on your,
so putting it in your adverb test limits,
and you explain these numbers and the one is normal.
So if you go up, let's go back to a couple of slides,
and you'll see that.
So you've got your liquid under your plastic limit.
So this is an adverb limit, actually.
It's one more thing.
Oh, go back to it.
Go forward.
Right there.
It's a bottom.
So a gray bottom right here.
So that those adverbs are, that's a liquid limit.
So that's a variety of three.
It's just that, it's basically telling you,
what we do is test on the place.
Sure.
And we do it when they're wet and when they're dry.
So we just keep adding water to the soil until,
when you get the liquid limit,
basically that's the definition when the soil has no more strength.
So if we have a moisture content of soil at 43,
and that's the liquid limit of the soil at 43,
we'd be walking in line.
So that's the very high of the moisture,
the low weight that's called the plastic limit.
And that's just being through drying out to get it.
One more moisture I call it the problem.
The wind and the wind of those tests, that's where the soil is.
It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a permute and it loses its phosphorus.
It's the solid fault of the wind, it's the phosphorus.
So, those were ranges.
As my, I'm not, the ranges typically look at more,
until the, the good thing is that if you didn't have so much water this would be good
so I'm saying, you can try out very quickly.
Have water took a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a.
That's what makes the soils move and they go up and down and they move and you may not see it if you're cut to the edge or you know
white roses of the here or sort of a truck and they cut it down for each and you saw the truck over it
You see almost like a lot of it the truck would go over and it would get down and then the truck will when over it would come out
It's an 80 minutes. It's something to see but that's that's the kind of soils that we have
They have a little bit more strength and they're they're out of the limits of the liquid
And they're just a little bit lower and so they let water in and then they tend to move a little bit
That's your country
Yeah, I was just so my curiosity was I understand the numbers are looking out from what was the base on what's the best of the
Well
Good term would be
Liquid that's fine. It's just we would like the moisture if you go back that I think go forward to slits
It's like the right here
So the liquid from the here happens to be 30% so at 35% wish with that clay
It turns into kind of super that have a strength if you could get the moisture down to 20
To start the pump
Well
Our moisture is 22% so we're a lot of the company of all the liquid and it's just enough
And it starts to move the better so if we could get the moisture somehow down
But what we would be asking is
So now we get somehow not get water in the line the rainfall when you have as much as it was or somehow we could raise my amount
Twenty feet and drain better to the notion
So that's not that not that having the best next test end is we can cut them to try to manage it gets all over again
And then you want to get something that's trying to get it away
So that's how we're going to try to manage that
It's live with the liquid that
And that's why streets cost the most money because we do have to do now
I mean to the school
I don't get to where you're based in
Because you have a good 100,000 block and then all parts
That's why a lot of the streets you'll see you see it's happens cracks all over
There are every three forms of quality of the fraction because you look at the quality of the fact
It looks kind of like that same crack and it's just because the streets movement up
You may not be able to see it but every time a truck roll over it, it's a move that is up and it's moving everywhere that it cracks
And so that's what we're trying to prevent with doing it with concrete or if we're doing it with that's what we're trying to make sure that
maybe it's a bigger base or maybe partly adding them these fibers down and you kind of kill our fibers that you can answer to the asphalt
or the huts just hold it and ask what we have for the make it so they can do without practice much.
I don't know if someone might have any kind of a body, you know.
Yeah, one of the things I get we had was I could think about it the same year now.
So a couple years ago I saw him and I said, hey, sorry, I didn't make sure we did this.
The city at one time had a complaint and it basically just could pulverize the asphalt pulverize the base tunnel.
And so what we had an idea was, hey, what if we bring over the reclaims of asphalt reclaim some of the base tunnel and maybe you know what the soil
and so what we did was just pile of test that it makes it all together and we added a little bit of cement in 3% cement from the base, 5% and 7% and with 5% cement we're going to get a reclaim the asphalt pavement that was built that could have some strength and it's called
It's very nice to be called cement tree in the base but it's basically a poor man and cement broke.
And then if we could overlay that with the better, then these are things that the sea could, you know, reclaim it, get there, reclaim it back.
They could, you know, you need to do all this in it.
They would just have to divide the concrete.
So instead of buying concrete, they would give the fires, they'd go to the right of the next and say, I want a leets in it because you just water it in cement.
And once they reclaim their air, they would place the cement on that and then use the reclaim or the next again, impact it and then you would have, you know, six to eight inch section of the wheat, a week's in it.
And then you put your asphalt pavement out of that.
But again, these are all the activities that the city could use to make it stretch their dollars instead of doing five blocks, kind of more floor construction, maybe they could do ten, fifteen blocks.
And this kind of reduced effort.
They don't have to take them into your own, call them off somewhere else, bring you materials in.
So the cost is kept just a little bit lower.
So we identified some of the streets that we thought would be good genders to try to find a better spot.
You just see how it came out in the trip work.
That might be an option to help stretch down what you can do.
Let's see, expect a long journey.
I think in the end it's going to be desert work for the city.
From the city can't work when you do.
I think it's still often work when the trucks that the trash truck thrown on the side.
I think our paper works and I've seen people do this.
Normally with the news I do this to that tree.
I felt when they before they put this man in health.
Push it to one side or another.
So take out two or three to the soil.
Put it back.
And then I'll continue.
So when it does, we'll have to, for instance, put on the water last door.
That will last just like a new street.
We're just trying to see if we can do that without having to help me.
So if you don't have to help me, then the cost will come down.
It's a different one.
But we're not touching the twice.
We're basically touching it one by one.
And if it could work, then this, I think, would, I think it would be a pilot test
the way that the approach should do it.
But I'm pretty certain that the last water in the asphalt streets,
because they don't have enough base to do it.
Typically, when we do a street, it will find a range of the last water in the floor.
It chooses to light it as crack, probably.
So it's really not an asphalt.
It's more of a base to it.
Because it's crack, and it's possible.
And underneath that we find many of the branches of the,
I could use a couple of red, red, red, red, red, red, or,
used to be brown, but they got from the, like, the usual.
Because it's an old base, and you crush it.
It's kind of, you creep.
So it's around and around.
It's pretty different, like, an arm rose, and even a depth.
If you were to use it now, you wouldn't want to,
we wouldn't want it much thicker than an or another branch.
But so this way, it's just trying to reuse,
what's our use.
And if we could do that.
We could do that.
We could use the stretch and dip that.
You know, any more sleep time.
It's definitely always different.
I mean, you can do it more often.
So we need to reclaim our reclaim.
Yeah.
We were running along here or something.
So what I asked them, and he said, we just sold it.
They sold it a lot, man.
Yeah.
I mean, I brought it to no one.
I didn't see it by a concrete point.
I mean, like, our concrete.
So we, we're not to figure out something because we obviously are a way far beyond
street repairs.
So, you know, we're finally starting to do utility projects,
a matter of trying to bring in.
The street projects.
I'm just trying to figure that out.
And one novel, I don't know how it works.
It had to work for everybody in the city.
But if we, if we reclaim now and made the trash truck running out,
that would take a lot of trucks off the ground.
And then I would try to get the cement trees with cement.
Treated streets with water.
I know that it works.
It's hard.
And the poor dairy trucker.
And we have a trash truck.
And it's fully loaded.
It's right on the one side.
That's a lot of weight.
Especially if the end of the ground.
So that's just a little bit of a challenge.
I think that's probably going to be at the end of the alleys.
And you all basically keep everything off the wind.
You know, the trucks are waiting for cars.
Some people are.
But we're trying to work with power.
And we're going to make the city's dollars.
It's very affordable.
I don't know if the people in the city are selling.
It's more affordable.
Thanks for every appreciate it.
You're going to make it.
that we're going to do.
We're not on an action model.
The NAM interested in very complex,
C111-112, root and root order,
the FG-NFB-4, root and root and root.
It serves as the use of water-line
in the place of projects and to the road and mill,
that's totally a problem.
So we have the machine that we've done,
the machine that we've done.
There are some updates there.
We did it through GIS, so we got this.
everything that you can do with this kind of
with the energy itself, the first I was in GIS,
but you see the one map has goes in my words.
The other map is just, you know,
it's up to the word that I removed.
So you can look at the different roads we have,
what's in, we have pictures on man,
and then you have a prize right there
so you click on the room, you can give you the estimate,
the road.
I know everybody sees the 16 million,
but you have to think, I mean, over a five million
and that is for the trip route.
It's a lot.
And then we'll get to the casual streets,
the individual streets.
If I had the money to do this,
the school would probably get this in a few days
so that you can get ready to try to plan a few lessons.
They're all, you know, you're definitely the same way.
Can you guys send it to the community, click back on the map.
So all the, all these lines I've taken in the list
we are going to, two years ago,
if the council approves the nine,
you do a geotech report on it.
So the go drill, the chairman,
the thing was that they asked all the thickness of the base
to see if it's worthwhile to spend the city's money on,
and over there, or just some of them just over there,
depending on the thickness of it.
Another cool thing about this is,
we also use some utility side
because we have one of them,
and then you ask all three down,
and let's replace the water line.
So the thickness, the depth of the rock,
because we've paid different amounts of,
if they contract with the rocker,
we can rock, then it costs more than it could afford
than it could afford in the straight soil.
So we use this report for the utility side,
and straight side, which is kind of the thing.
We'll also be doing a couple of other down
because, you know, you get a value with a mario
and they're trapped down there.
They're doing a couple of boars for the turn pie crossing,
because we have a water line of heat.
The period housing up there, there's one heat.
We do have issues up there on the pond,
we're stuck in another feed up there.
And then they're doing, we have to have a geotec,
every time we cross the railroad,
or a permit for the water,
we're doing that as part of this.
So we're happy to answer any questions,
with construction by your changing frequently.
We needed the best we could on my youth, but, you know,
I talked to you a few different things with me
and I needed a mill and overlay versus a total of reconstruct.
So we're trying to get as many mill and overlay as we possibly can.
But we'll be trucker out.
Best of the time we'll take to do that.
Well, that's probably going to take care of the youth.
I don't think so on.
Because we have a business design,
I mean, once we get the design, we need to do that.
And then, we'll eventually make sure we come almost as year
that we can identify as we do.
We'll have six or four box out of that.
I was thinking...
I think we have to do that in a section,
just to just...
So we could help the tractor keep flowing
and do what they have about the structure and the city.
The one out of the structure is the truck tractor.
We're very not just the structure.
You don't know, an A3.
We love the state of the...
Yeah.
We tell the state.
And we would end the meeting.
When we took the truck back down before,
we turned on their history to turn the different streets.
And that's the way some of them turned on the truck.
We did it in a turn on the act of the act of the act.
Yeah.
So...
Well, there's plenty of elements in our own streets.
But the kind of tractor on...
They should be a good solution.
Yeah.
And then one thing we did with the city
is Robert Williams took the photos of all the streets
of where to be read down.
So a few click on him.
He was right next to you.
Yeah.
We were on the work with him.
And then he could see how...
Everyone would be streaks at the red and look very similar.
You could...
This is how I get a correct answer.
Which means that the sort of...
It's too soft for the kind of stone in that direction.
Yeah.
So most of them work very similar.
There aren't bit of a thing to judge.
It's like...
Try and know, or whatever, that you could say.
He just...
He's quite just like...
It's like...
Just like...
And then we took all the photos of the ones in,
In the photo of it.
Just to be...
Get it done.
It doesn't work...
If you want to get on the one, we need to get on.
And then...
This is the cause.
And we'll go to another...
To part of it.
It's a computer source building back to where it's called.
Some of the street construction Central Equator...
in the world of the world, and I haven't walked in on that one, but 30 or 30 pieces.
Some other proposals are all from what we discussed.
We might be in one side of the street, and we'll switch to you in the south side.
In the end, the estimates were trying to have done it all the same manner so that people would be charged.
There is treatment done in the same way, so it's not going to go through anything.
Hey, what's the rate in my can?
There's just something to pause if you look at it and tell it if there's any caution.
If they believe I'm getting the streets out there, if I'm getting out of the time, I'm going to discuss that.
What's all good street corn plants over there?
Would you be at the front of the street again?
And then we're in the process of getting a second one and you've done some of the things that you have.
Even though it's a disaster, it's just with questions.
And we've worked with that and worked with the government that we've prepared for the next time.
We're trying to get that into it, so we can have something up with that in the work.
Usually, in a way that it's a power to look at, if we're doing it online, we blend out of it.
And if anybody else is going to have to do it.
So, and we don't really want to talk a lot about it tonight, but there is some, if you remember here,
again, the form of being here, we put in for the brick grant.
We were not expecting for the brick grant, but it appears that maybe some other funding and some other grants,
that they are possibly looking at us at, so they've asked us to submit this one information.
So that could be a game changer for us.
I've awarded one of those grants down for you.
Some of those were to speak for the import.
I'm excited about that one, I will be.
I'm excited.
Yeah.
And I mean, something to them that I stress the people is, you know, we're fixing these for, I think,
about 100 years.
How do you flood them in?
But I mean, everybody knows we have more fickle.
I think they're still on us, but I mean, different things.
So we would just be able to design for the best that we could.
And that project.
That's one of those.
It's one of those.
So it's the one because I think I felt right when I saw this, and I think I like to answer this.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Thank you for your attention.
Please send us a report.
I'm going to put it into the position of this being,
I'm going to slap the boards.
Well, the trucking, being out of it.
Follow the gun.
I'm going to do it.
I'll see you in the next episode.
Bye.